http://www.usssa.com/privacy

Login
{{item.title}}
Login
{{item.title}}
United States Specialty Sports Association Privacy Statement
Your privacy and security are important to us. Because we gather certain types of information about United States Specialty Sports Association, Inc. ("USSSA") users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to support@USSSA.com. NOTE: USSSA cannot accept information from individuals who are under 14 years of age without first obtaining express parental consent.
Capture and Use of Information
REGISTRATION
If you participate in USSSA activities (event registration, message boards, etc.) on USSSA, you may be asked to register for a free ID and password and/or to provide information on event-registration forms. Unique identifiers, such as IDs and passwords, are collected to verify your identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. Your contact information may also be used to contact you when necessary for customer service reasons. Financial information that is collected is used only to bill you for products and services that you specifically request.
COOKIES
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Generally, cookies work by assigning to your computer a unique number that has no meaning outside of our site. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information; we use them to provide features such as personalization, to save your member ID and to keep track various items. We may also use cookies to assist us in delivering content specific to your interests. Additionally, after you've entered your member ID and password during a session on our service, we save that information so you don't have to re-enter it repeatedly during that session. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Not accepting cookies may make certain features of USSSA unavailable to you.
IP ADDRESS
We may use your IP address to identify you, to administer our Web site and to assist in diagnosing problems with our server.
Additional Uses of Information
All of the information we collect, both what you tell us and what we collect through the use of cookies, is used to personalize your account, to customize our services and to allow our customer service representatives to contact you when necessary. It is USSSA' policy not to release any personally identifying information about you without your consent (usually obtained through an "opt-out" option that you may select when providing the information). In most cases, information will be released only on an aggregated basis (meaning that the information from many USSSA users is grouped together in a way that does not disclose the personal information of any particular user). We may use contact information that you provide to send you information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. USSSA will disclose personal information about an individual user if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with an applicable law or valid legal process.
SPECIAL NOTE FOR USERS ACCESSING USSSAWITHIB A FRAME
USSSA has partnered with various web sites ("Framing Sites"), allowing users of those Framing Sites to register for events and to otherwise use the USSSA services within a frame and without leaving the Framing Site. In some cases, USSSA has agreed to provide to the Framing Site personal information collected from people who make use of the USSSA services from the Framing Site (that is, within a frame and without leaving the Framing Site). In these cases, please be aware that the Framing Site operates independently from, and may have privacy and security policies wholly different from, USSSA. If you wish to make use of the USSSA services, but do not wish to have your information shared with third parties, please access our services directly, and not from a Framing Site.
General Privacy Information
USSSA makes various public forums (such as message boards, chat rooms or news groups) available to its users. When you disclose personal information in such public forums, that information can be collected and used by others in various ways, including by sending unsolicited messages. You are solely responsible for any postings you make on public forums on USSSA, and for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. Further, the USSSA web site contains links to partners, advertisers and third party Internet sites and services that may collect data in connection with registrations, promotions, e-commerce, etc. USSSA is also linked to by, and in some cases framed by, certain partner web sites. Each of the web sites (linked from USSSA, or linking to USSSA) each have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of USSSA, and USSSA has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Security
USSSA uses a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Credit card numbers are encrypted in USSSA' secure database which is located behind a firewall. Personal information collected on USSSA is stored in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public. All credit card and registration information supplied by users is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. USSSA' technology department conducts frequent site-security audits.
Protecting Yourself
You can help to protect your information by safeguarding your USSSA password, using caution and discretion when posting information on public areas of the USSSA Web site.
USSSA' Practices Regarding Cookies
USSSA uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to:
Access your information when you "sign in," so that we can provide you with customized content, such as Personal Settings.
Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using USSSA services. Display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on USSSA.Com
Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.
Conduct research to improve USSSA content and services.
Require you to re-enter your USSSA password after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences
You may request deletion of your USSSA account by sending an email to support@USSSA.com.
1996 - 2020 © All Rights Reserved.
